A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.1, Series 100 International - Series 257 Virgin Islands, U.S.A. FA386a
Rockefeller Archive Center
- United States, 1909-1974; 200; 28 Cubic Feet; 69 __Boxes __28 cubic feet
  - Institute for Government Research, May 1914-May 1915 (Box 26, Folder 294)
  - Institute for Government Research, May 1914-May 1915 (Box 26, Folder 295)
  - Institute for Government Research, May 1914-May 1915 (Box 26, Folder 296)
  - Institute for Government Research, June 1915-1925 (Box 27, Folder 297)
  - Institute for Government Research, June 1915-1925 (Box 27, Folder 298)
  - Institute for Government Research, June 1915-1925 (Box 27, Folder 299)
  - Institute for Government Research, June 1915-1925 (Box 27, Folder 300)
  - Institute for International Education - Ladd, John, 1948-1949 (Box 27, Folder 301)
  - Institute for International Education - Ladd, John - Reports, 1949; 2 Items (Box 27, Folder 302)
  - Institute for International Education - Richter, Werner, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 303)
  - International Health Division - Exhibits, 1936-1943 (Box 27, Folder 304)
  - International Health Division - Exhibits, 1936-1943 (Box 27, Folder 305)
  - International Health Division - Exhibits - Reports and Pamphlets, 1938-1940; 3 Items (Box 27, Folder 306)
  - Jackson Memorial Laboratory - Genetics Symposium, 1954-1955 (Box 27, Folder 307)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Biostatics, 1939 (Box 27, Folder 308)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Biostatics, 1947-1951 (Box 27, Folder 309)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Biostatics - Report, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 310)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Diphtheria, 1941 (Box 27, Folder 311)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Diphtheria, 1942-1948 (Box 28, Folder 312)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Diphtheria - Reports and Reprints, 1941-1947; 11 items contained in folders 313-314. (Box 28, Folder 313)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Diphtheria - Reports and Reprints, 1941-1947; 11 items contained in folders 313-314. (Box 28, Folder 314)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Fluke Disease, 1921-1922 (Box 28, Folder 315)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Freedman, Ruth - Travel Grant, Public Health Nursing, 1951-1953 (Box 28, Folder 316)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Rodent Ecology - Empty Folder (Box 28, Folder 317)
    Material originally filed in this folder is now available in RG 1.2, Series 200, Boxes 58-59, Folders 478-481.
  - Johns Hopkins University - Syphilis, 1936-December 1939 (Box 28, Folder 318)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Syphilis, 1936-December 1939 (Box 28, Folder 319)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Syphilis, 1936-December 1939 (Box 28, Folder 320)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Syphilis, 1936-December 1939 (Box 28, Folder 321)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Syphilis, 1940-1949 (Box 29, Folder 322)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Syphilis, 1940-1949 (Box 29, Folder 323)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Syphilis, 1940-1949 (Box 29, Folder 324)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Syphilis, 1940-1949 (Box 29, Folder 325)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Syphilis, 1940-1949 (Box 29, Folder 326)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Syphilis - Reports, 1938-1947; 11 items contained in folders 327-328. (Box 29, Folder 327)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Syphilis - Reports, 1938-1947; 11 items contained in folders 327-328. (Box 29, Folder 328)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Taxonomic Center, 1945-1952 (Box 29, Folder 329)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Taxonomic Center, 1945-1952 (Box 29, Folder 330)
  - Journal of Industrial Hygiene, 1932-1941 (Box 30, Folder 331)
  - Julius Rosenwald Fund, 1929-1933 (Box 30, Folder 332)
  - Lattimore, Owen D. (Far Eastern Studies), 1933-1955 (Box 30, Folder 333)
  - Lattimore, Owen D. (Far Eastern Studies), 1933-1955 (Box 30, Folder 334)
  - Layman's Missionary Movement, New York City, 1914-1916 (Box 30, Folder 335)
  - Legal Aid Society, 1914-1916 (Box 30, Folder 336)
  - Lewis, Hobart D. (RF Staff), 1929-1934 (Box 30, Folder 337)
  - Library of Congress - Russian Collections - Microfilming, 1950-1954 (Box 30, Folder 338)
  - Library of Congress - Slavic Collections, 1950-1951 (Box 30, Folder 339)
  - Maryland - Health (McCallum, James Angus), 1952-1953 (Box 30, Folder 340)
  - Maryland State Planning Commission - Medical Care, 1951-1955 (Box 30, Folder 341)
  - Maryland State Planning Commission - Medical Care, 1951-1955 (Box 30, Folder 342)
  - Maryland State Planning Commission - Medical Care - Reports, 1952-1955; 4 Items (Box 30, Folder 343)
  - McCollum, E. V. - Historical Record - (Powdered Milk Investigation), 1920 (Box 30, Folder 344)
  - Midwest Inter-Library Corporation, 1949-1955 (Box 30, Folder 345)
  - Midwest Inter-Library Corporation, 1949-1955 (Box 30, Folder 346)
  - Midwest Inter-Library Corporation - Reports, 1949-1953; 10 Items (Box 31, Folder 347)
  - Ministers and Missionaries Benefit Board of the Northern Baptists Convention, 1915-1929 (Box 31, Folder 348)
  - Murine Typhus, 1944-1951 (Box 31, Folder 349)
  - Murine Typhus, 1944-1951 (Box 31, Folder 350)
  - Murine Typhus, 1944-1951 (Box 31, Folder 351)
  - Murine Typhus, 1944-1951 (Box 31, Folder 352)
  - Murine Typhus, 1944-1951 (Box 31, Folder 353)
  - Murine Typhus, 1944-1951 (Box 31, Folder 354)
  - Murine Typhus, 1944-1951 (Box 31, Folder 355)
  - Murine Typhus, 1944-1951 (Box 31, Folder 356)
  - Murine Typhus - Report, 1945 (Box 31, Folder 357)
  - National Association for Mental Health, Inc., 1951-1958 (Box 32, Folder 358)
  - National Child Labor Committee, 1914 (Box 32, Folder 359)
  - National Citizens' Committee for United Nations Day, 1952-1953 (Box 32, Folder 360)
  - National Citizens' Committee for United Nations Day - Reports and Pamphlets, 1952; 2 Items (Box 32, Folder 361)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - Minutes, 1913-1936 (Box 32, Folder 362)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, 1909-April 1916 (Box 32, Folder 363)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, 1909-April 1916 (Box 32, Folder 364)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, 1909-April 1916 (Box 32, Folder 365)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, 1909-April 1916 (Box 32, Folder 366)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, 1909-April 1916 (Box 32, Folder 367)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, May 1916-December 1916 (Box 33, Folder 368)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, May 1916-December 1916 (Box 33, Folder 369)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - (RF DR 109, 109a, 129), January-March 1917 (Box 33, Folder 370)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, April-December 1917 (Box 33, Folder 371)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - (RF DR 130), January-September 1918 (Box 33, Folder 372)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, October-December 1918 (Box 33, Folder 373)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - (RF DR 189), January-May 1919 (Box 33, Folder 374)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, June 1919-1923 (Box 33, Folder 375)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, June 1919-1923 (Box 33, Folder 376)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, June 1919-1923 (Box 33, Folder 377)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, June 1919-1923 (Box 33, Folder 378)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, June 1919-1923 (Box 33, Folder 379)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, 1924-March 1939 (Box 34, Folder 380)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, 1924-March 1939 (Box 34, Folder 381)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, 1924-March 1939 (Box 34, Folder 382)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, 1924-March 1939 (Box 34, Folder 383)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, 1924-March 1939 (Box 34, Folder 384)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, 1924-March 1939 (Box 34, Folder 385)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, 1924-March 1939 (Box 34, Folder 386)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, 1924-March 1939 (Box 34, Folder 387)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, 1924-March 1939 (Box 34, Folder 388)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, 1924-March 1939 (Box 34, Folder 389)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, 1924-March 1939 (Box 34, Folder 390)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, April 1939-1945 (Box 35, Folder 391)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, April 1939-1945 (Box 35, Folder 392)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, April 1939-1945 (Box 35, Folder 393)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - Reports (RF DR 137), 1916-1924; 4 Items (Box 35, Folder 394)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - Report, 1925 (Box 35, Folder 395)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - Reports, 1933-1936; 4 Items (Box 35, Folder 396)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - Report, Undated, After 1936 (Box 35, Folder 397)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - Reports, 1937-1938; 4 Items (Box 35, Folder 398)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - Reports, 1942; 2 Items (Box 35, Folder 399)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - Reprints and Pamphlets, 1931-1939; 6 Items (Box 35, Folder 400)
  - National Councils, 1935-1936 (Box 36, Folder 401)
  - National Councils - Report and Working Papers - (RF DR 502), 1935 (Box 36, Folder 402)
  - National Education Association - German Educators, 1948-1949 (Box 36, Folder 403)
  - National Education Association - Public Education In Occupied Countries - Report, 1950 (Box 36, Folder 406)
  - National Fuel Gas Company, 1940-1943 (Box 36, Folder 407)
  - National Fuel Gas Company, 1940-1943 (Box 36, Folder 408)
  - National Health Council, 1921-1924 (Box 36, Folder 409)
  - National Health Council - Report on President's Commission, 1952-1953 (Box 36, Folder 410)
  - National Highways Protective Society, 1914-1915 (Box 36, Folder 411)
  - National Information Bureau, 1919-1926 (Box 36, Folder 412)
  - National Institute of Health - Dental Survey, 1934-1938 (Box 36, Folder 413)
  - National League on Urban Conditions Among Negroes, 1914-1915 (Box 36, Folder 414)
  - National Research Council, 1918-1927 (Box 36, Folder 415)
  - National Research Council, 1918-1927 (Box 36, Folder 416)
  - National Research Council - Institute of Physics and Chemistry, 1917-1920 (Box 37, Folder 417)
  - National Research Council - Research Aid Fund, 1929 (Box 37, Folder 418)
  - National Research Council - Research Aid Fund, 1930-December 1935 (Box 37, Folder 419)
  - National Research Council - Research Aid Fund, 1930-December 1935 (Box 37, Folder 420)
  - National Research Council - Research Aid Fund, 1930-December 1935 (Box 37, Folder 421)
  - National Research Council - Research Aid Fund, 1930-December 1935 (Box 37, Folder 422)
  - National Research Council - Research Aid Fund, 1930-December 1935 (Box 37, Folder 423)
  - National Research Council - Research Aid Fund, 1930-December 1935 (Box 37, Folder 424)
  - National Research Council - Research Aid Fund, 1930-December 1935 (Box 37, Folder 425)
  - National Research Council - Research Aid Fund, 1930-December 1935 (Box 37, Folder 426)
  - National Research Council - Research Aid Fund, 1930-December 1935 (Box 37, Folder 427)
  - National Research Council - Research Aid Fund, 1930-December 1935 (Box 37, Folder 428)
  - National Research Council - Research Aid Fund, 1936-1949 (Box 38, Folder 429)
  - National Research Council - Research Aid Fund, 1936-1949 (Box 38, Folder 430)
  - National Research Council - Research Aid Fund, 1936-1949 (Box 38, Folder 431)
  - National Research Council - Research Aid Fund - Reports, 1929-1938; 16 items contained in folders 432-435. (Box 38, Folder 432)
  - National Research Council - Research Aid Fund - Reports, 1929-1938; 16 items contained in folders 432-435. (Box 38, Folder 433)
  - National Research Council - Research Aid Fund - Reports, 1929-1938; 16 items contained in folders 432-435. (Box 38, Folder 434)
  - National Research Council - Research Aid Fund - Reports, 1929-1938; 16 items contained in folders 432-435. (Box 38, Folder 435)
  - National Research Council - Sex Research, 1927-1935 (Box 38, Folder 436)
  - National Research Council - Sex Research, 1927-1935 (Box 38, Folder 437)
  - National Research Council - Sex Research, 1927-1935 (Box 38, Folder 438)
  - National Research Council - Sex Research, 1927-1935 (Box 38, Folder 439)
  - National Research Council - Sex Research, 1936-1960 (Box 39, Folder 440)
  - National Research Council - Sex Research, 1936-1960 (Box 39, Folder 441)
  - National Research Council - Sex Research, 1936-1960 (Box 39, Folder 442)
  - National Research Council - Sex Research, 1936-1960 (Box 39, Folder 443)
  - National Research Council - Sex Research, 1936-1960 (Box 39, Folder 444)
  - National Research Council - Sex Research, 1936-1960 (Box 39, Folder 445)
  - National Research Council - Sex Research, 1936-1960 (Box 39, Folder 446)
  - National Research Council - Sex Research, 1936-1960 (Box 39, Folder 447)
  - National Research Council - Sex Research, 1936-1960 (Box 39, Folder 448)
  - National Research Council - Sex Research, 1936-1960 (Box 39, Folder 449)
  - National Research Council - Sex Research, 1936-1960 (Box 39, Folder 450)
  - National Research Council - Sex Research, 1936-1960 (Box 39, Folder 451)
  - National Research Council - Sex Research, 1961-1968 (Box 40, Folder 452)
  - National Research Council - Sex Research - Reports, 1922-1956; 14 items contained in folders 453-455. (Box 40, Folder 453)
  - National Research Council - Sex Research - Reports, 1922-1956; 14 items contained in folders 453-455. (Box 40, Folder 454)
  - National Research Council - Sex Research - Reports, 1922-1956; 14 items contained in folders 453-455. (Box 40, Folder 455)
  - National Research Council - Sex Research - Reprints and Pamphlets, 1948-1960; 6 Items (Box 40, Folder 456)
  - National Research Council - Sex Research - Kinsey, 1943-April 1949 (Box 40, Folder 457)
  - National Research Council - Sex Research - Kinsey, 1943-April 1949 (Box 40, Folder 458)
  - National Research Council - Sex Research - Kinsey, 1943-April 1949 (Box 40, Folder 459)
  - National Research Council - Sex Research - Kinsey, 1943-April 1949 (Box 40, Folder 460)
  - National Research Council - Sex Research - Kinsey, 1943-April 1949 (Box 40, Folder 461)
  - National Research Council - Sex Research - Kinsey, May 1949-1954 (Box 41, Folder 462)
  - National Research Council - Sex Research - Kinsey, May 1949-1954 (Box 41, Folder 463)
  - National Research Council - Sex Research - Kinsey, May 1949-1954 (Box 41, Folder 464)
  - National Research Council - Sex Research - Kinsey, May 1949-1954 (Box 41, Folder 465)
  - National Research Council - Sex Research - Kinsey - Report, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 466)
  - National Research Council - Sex Research - Kinsey - Reports and Reprints, 1947-1948; 6 Items (Box 41, Folder 467)
  - National Social Welfare Assembly - Youth Division, January-April 1948 (Box 41, Folder 468)
  - National Social Welfare Assembly - Youth Division, May 1948-1953 (Box 42, Folder 469)
  - National Social Welfare Assembly - Youth Division, May 1948-1953 (Box 42, Folder 470)
  - National Social Welfare Assembly - Youth Division, May 1948-1953 (Box 42, Folder 471)
  - National Social Welfare Assembly - Youth Division, May 1948-1953 (Box 42, Folder 472)
  - National Social Welfare Assembly - Youth Division, May 1948-1953 (Box 42, Folder 473)
  - National Social Welfare Assembly - Youth Division, May 1948-1953 (Box 42, Folder 474)
  - National Social Welfare Assembly - Youth Division, May 1948-1953 (Box 42, Folder 475)
  - National Social Welfare Assembly - Youth Division, May 1948-1953 (Box 42, Folder 476)
  - National Social Welfare Assembly - Youth Division, May 1948-1953 (Box 42, Folder 477)
  - National Social Welfare Assembly - Youth Division, May 1948-1953 (Box 42, Folder 478)
  - National Social Welfare Assembly - Youth Division - Report, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 479)
  - National Social Welfare Assembly - Youth Division - Reports, 1951-1952; 6 items contained in folders 480-481. (Box 43, Folder 480)
  - National Social Welfare Assembly - Youth Division - Reports, 1951-1952; 6 items contained in folders 480-481. (Box 43, Folder 481)
  - National Society for the Prevention of Blindness, 1913-1919 (Box 43, Folder 482)
  - National Society for the Prevention of Blindness, 1913-1919 (Box 43, Folder 483)
  - National Transit Company, 1936-1943 (Box 43, Folder 484)
  - National Travelers Aid Association, 1951 (Box 43, Folder 485)
  - New Jersey Baptist Convention, 1914-1916 (Box 43, Folder 486)
  - New School for Social Research - Fink, Eugen - (Visit, Philosophy), 1914-1949 (Box 43, Folder 487)
  - New School for Social Research - Heimann, Edward - (Travel Grant, Economics), 1948-1950 (Box 43, Folder 488)
  - New School for Social Research - Vambery, Rustem - (Refugee Scholar, Criminology), 1939-1942 (Box 43, Folder 489)
  - New School for Social Research - Vambery, Rustem - (Refugee Scholar, Criminology), 1939-1942 (Box 43, Folder 490)
  - New York Association for the Blind, 1914 (Box 43, Folder 491)
  - New York Baptist City Society, 1955-1973 (Box 44, Folder 492)
  - New York Baptist City Society, 1955-1973 (Box 44, Folder 493)
  - New York Child Labor Committee, 1914 (Box 44, Folder 494)
  - New York City Baptist Mission Society, 1915-1916 (Box 44, Folder 495)
  - New York City Police Department, 1916 (Box 44, Folder 496)
  - New York City Training School for Dental Hygienists, 1916-1918 (Box 44, Folder 497)
  - New York Transit Company, 1940-1943 (Box 44, Folder 498)
  - New York Transit Company, 1940-1943 (Box 44, Folder 499)
  - New York University - Bayne, Helen - (Travel Grant, Library Science), 1952-1953; 1217287 (Box 44, Folder 500)
  - New York University - Rosenberg, Conrad - (Travel Grant, Medicine), 1951-1952 (Box 44, Folder 501)
  - New York University - Work Student Exchange Program, 1948-1951 (Box 44, Folder 502)
  - New York University - Work Student Exchange Program, 1948-1951 (Box 44, Folder 503)
  - New York University - Work Student Exchange Program, 1948-1951 (Box 44, Folder 504)
  - New York University - Work Student Exchange Program, 1948-1951 (Box 44, Folder 505)
  - New York University - Work Student Exchange Program, 1948-1951 (Box 44, Folder 506)
  - New York University - Work Student Exchange Program - Reports, 1949-1950; 6 items contained in folders 507-508. (Box 44, Folder 507)
  - New York University - Work Student Exchange Program - Reports, 1949-1950; 6 items contained in folders 507-508. (Box 44, Folder 508)
  - Nomenclature of Death, 1920 (Box 45, Folder 509)
  - Oberlaender Trust - Deposed Scholars Study, 1939-1947 (Box 45, Folder 510)
  - Oberlaender Trust - Deposed Scholars Study, 1939-1947 (Box 45, Folder 511)
  - Ohio Baptist Convention, 1915 (Box 45, Folder 512)
  - Ohio State University - Heller, Herman - (Refugee Scholar, Political Science and Public Law), 1933 (Box 45, Folder 513)
  - Palisades Interstate Park Commission, 1915-1916 (Box 45, Folder 514)
  - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Pamphlets, 1918-1920; 5 Items (Box 45, Folder 515)
  - Pan American Sanitary Bureau - Building Purchase, 1945-1953 (Box 45, Folder 516)
  - Pan American Sanitary Bureau - Nursing, 1947-1948 (Box 45, Folder 517)
  - Parents Publishing Association, 1925-1950 (Box 46, Folder 518)
  - Parents Publishing Association, 1925-1950 (Box 46, Folder 519)
  - Parents Publishing Association, 1925-1950 (Box 46, Folder 520)
  - Parks and Playgrounds Association, 1914-1916 (Box 46, Folder 521)
  - Peoples Institute, 1916 (Box 46, Folder 522)
  - Personnel Selection, 1936-1938 (Box 46, Folder 523)
  - Police Society of Westchester County, 1914-1916 (Box 46, Folder 524)
  - Princeton University - United States Exchange Program, 1950-1955 (Box 46, Folder 525)
  - Prison Association of New York, 1914-1916 (Box 46, Folder 526)
  - Public Education Association, 1914-1916 (Box 46, Folder 527)
  - Queens College, New York - Alewyn, Richard - (Travel Grant, German Literature), 1949-1952 (Box 46, Folder 528)
  - Refugee Scholars, 1936-November 1940 (Box 46, Folder 529)
  - Refugee Scholars, 1936-November 1940 (Box 46, Folder 530)
  - Refugee Scholars, 1936-November 1940 (Box 46, Folder 531)
  - Refugee Scholars, 1936-November 1940 (Box 46, Folder 532)
  - Refugee Scholars, 1936-November 1940 (Box 46, Folder 533)
  - Refugee Scholars, December 1940-1963 (Box 47, Folder 534)
  - Refugee Scholars, December 1940-1963 (Box 47, Folder 535)
  - Refugee Scholars, December 1940-1963 (Box 47, Folder 536)
  - Refugee Scholars, December 1940-1963 (Box 47, Folder 537)
  - Refugee Scholars, December 1940-1963 (Box 47, Folder 538)
  - Refugee Scholars, December 1940-1963 (Box 47, Folder 539)
  - Refugee Scholars, December 1940-1963 (Box 47, Folder 540)
  - Refugee Scholars, December 1940-1963 (Box 47, Folder 541)
  - Refugee Scholars, December 1940-1963 (Box 47, Folder 542)
  - Refugee Scholars - Reports, 1939-1940; 4 Items (Box 47, Folder 543)
  - Refugee Scholars - Report - Appleget, Thomas B. - "Special Research Aid Fund for Deposed Scholars, 1933-1939" - Ref-1 (Box 47, Folder 544)
  - Refugee Scholars - Report - Appleget, Thomas B. - "Refugee Scholars Program, 1940" RF DR 555 - Ref-2 (Box 47, Folder 545)
  - Refugee Scholars - Report - Appleget, Thomas B. - "The Foundation's Experience with Refugee Scholars" - Ref-3, 1946 (Box 47, Folder 0545a)
  - Refugee Scholars - Benoit-Levy, Jean - (Motion Pictures), 1941-1945 (Box 47, Folder 546)
  - Refugee Scholars - Benoit-Levy, Jean - (Motion Pictures), 1941-1945 (Box 47, Folder 547)
  - Refugee Scholars - Bickerman, Elias - (Ancient History), 1940-1945 (Box 48, Folder 548)
  - Refugee Scholars - Bickerman, Elias - (Ancient History), 1940-1945 (Box 48, Folder 549)
  - Refugee Scholars - Bloch, Marc - (Economic and Social History), 1940-1942 (Box 48, Folder 550)
  - Refugee Scholars - Bloch, Marc - (Economic and Social History), 1940-1942 (Box 48, Folder 551)
  - Refugee Scholars - Bonn, Moritz - (Economics), 1935-1945 (Box 48, Folder 552)
  - Refugee Scholars - Bonn, Moritz - (Economics), 1935-1945 (Box 48, Folder 553)
  - Refugee Scholars - Bonnet, Henri - (International Relations), 1940-1944 (Box 48, Folder 554)
  - Refugee Scholars - Bonnet, Henri - (International Relations), 1940-1944 (Box 48, Folder 555)
  - Refugee Scholars - Boris, Guilbert - (Arabic), 1941-1943 (Box 48, Folder 556)
  - Refugee Scholars - Boris, Guilbert - (Arabic), 1941-1943 (Box 48, Folder 557)
  - Refugee Scholars - Brodersen, Arvid - (Sociology), 1940-1942 (Box 48, Folder 558)
  - Refugee Scholars - Brodersen, Arvid - (Sociology), 1940-1942 (Box 48, Folder 559)
  - Refugee Scholars - Brook, Warner F. - (Economics and Political Science), 1940-1945 (Box 48, Folder 560)
  - Refugee Scholars - Brook, Warner F. - (Economics and Political Science), 1940-1945 (Box 48, Folder 561)
  - Refugee Scholars - Bruck, Herman - (Physics), 1940-1941 (Box 48, Folder 562)
  - Refugee Scholars - Burchardt, Fritz - (Economics), 1934-1941 (Box 48, Folder 563)
  - Refugee Scholars - Cahn, Theophile - (Biochemistry), 1940-1942 (Box 48, Folder 564)
  - Refugee Scholars - Cahn, Theophile - (Biochemistry), 1940-1942 (Box 48, Folder 565)
  - Refugee Scholars - Castillejo, Jose - (Roman Law), 1940-1941 (Box 48, Folder 566)
  - Refugee Scholars - Cohen, Gustave - (Romance Languages), 1942-1948 (Box 49, Folder 567)
  - Refugee Scholars - Conference, 1941 (Box 49, Folder 568)
  - Refugee Scholars - Dennery, Etienne - (International Relations), 1940-1944 (Box 49, Folder 569)
  - Refugee Scholars - Dennery, Etienne - (International Relations), 1940-1944 (Box 49, Folder 570)
  - Refugee Scholars - Desaussure, Raymond - (Psychiatry), 1940-1944 (Box 49, Folder 571)
  - Refugee Scholars - Desaussure, Raymond - (Psychiatry), 1940-1944 (Box 49, Folder 572)
  - Refugee Scholars - De Terra, Helmut - (Geology, Geography, Anthropology), 1940-1942 (Box 49, Folder 573)